# CONTACT

- +966534081115
- Fmutawa223@gmail.com
- Eastern Province, Saudi Arabia

# **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Science
 Computer Information Systems
 University of Indianapolis 2017

# **SKILLS**

- Statistical Analysis
- Machine Learning
- Data Mining
- Computer languages (R, Python, SLQ, etc.)
- Data Science
- Data Analysis
- Data Visualization
- Statistics
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe After Effects
- Adobe Photoshop
- Microsoft Office
- Problem-solving
- Communication
- Teamwork
- Innovative thinking
- · Critical thinking
- Attention To Detail
- Time Management
- Presentation Skills
- Communication Skills
- Stress Management

# **LANGUAGE**

Arabic

Native

**English** 

Fluent

# Fatimah Almutawa

# **PROFILE**

Enthusiastic Computer Information Systems Graduate with a great academic experience in Statistical Modeling, Data Analysis, and Data Programming. Accustomed to performing in deadline-driven environments with an emphasis on working within budget requirements. Looking forward to joining a company that allows me to learn and grow my skills and contributes to a forward-thinking and fast-moving industry where I can share all my skills.

### **EXPERIENCE**

# **Executive Secretary**

Rawabi Electric | Dammam | May 2018 - Present

- Work with the wider development team.
- Generate regular reports and update the database.
- Provides high-level administrative support and assistance to the Executive Director and/or other assigned leadership staff.
- Conduct research and prepare presentations.
- Performs office tasks including maintaining records, ordering supplies, and performing basic bookkeeping.
- Organize logistics and plan events.
- Facilitate communication within the company.
- Improve training plan for newcomers to be more effective.
- Performs additional duties as assigned by executives.

#### **Training Developer**

Rawabi Electric | Dammam | Nov 2021 - Present

- Create a training program from scratch that includes training scenarios, training references, and training videos.
- Record voice and videos to richen the training.
- Gather all materials and created a whole training program for each position in the company.
- Evaluates emerging training techniques and tools.
- Designs curriculum and delivers training for college staff on various subjects including using college-supported software and tools
- Design, plan, organize, or direct orientation and training programs for employees or customers.
- Develop alternative training methods if expected improvements are not seen.
- Evaluate training materials prepared by instructors, such as outlines, text, or handouts.

# **AWARDS**

**Appreciation Letter** 

Rawabi Holding | 2018

Appreciation of volunteering in several company events.

#### Buyer

Rawabi Electric | Dammam | Mar 2021 - Nov 2021

- Purchase goods, materials, components, or services in line with specified cost, quality, and delivery targets.
- Build relationships with suppliers and negotiate with them for the best pricing.
- Process requisitions and update management on the status of orders.
- Arrange transport of goods and track orders to ensure timely delivery.
- Update inventory and ensure that stock levels are kept at appropriate levels.

# **CERTIFICATES**

**Classroom Communication** 

University of Indianapolis | 2017

Motion Graphics: Movie Title

University of Indianapolis | 2017

**English Language Certificate** 

Internexus Indiana | 2013

Stress Management

ProCloud Training Center | 2022

**Supervising Others** 

ProCloud Training Center | 2022